<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<fmg>
<compression>None</compression>
<version>DarkSouls3</version>
<bigendian>False</bigendian>
<entries>
<text id="2100">Perfil</text>
<text id="2500">Restablecer asignaciones</text>
<text id="3000">Configurar potencia de vibración de control</text>
<text id="3001">%null%</text>
<text id="3002">%null%</text>
<text id="3003">%null%</text>
<text id="3004">%null%</text>
<text id="3005">%null%</text>
<text id="3006">%null%</text>
<text id="3007">%null%</text>
<text id="3008">%null%</text>
<text id="3009">%null%</text>
<text id="3010">Asignar botones del control</text>
<text id="3011">%null%</text>
<text id="3012">%null%</text>
<text id="3013">%null%</text>
<text id="3014">%null%</text>
<text id="3015">%null%</text>
<text id="3016">%null%</text>
<text id="3017">%null%</text>
<text id="3018">%null%</text>
<text id="3019">%null%</text>
<text id="3020">Presiona un botón para asignar esta acción</text>
<text id="4101">No se puede conectar a la red.
Volviendo al menú de título...</text>
<text id="4102">Se perdió la conexión con el servidor de juego de ELDEN RING.
Volviendo al menú de título...</text>
<text id="4160">Se interrumpió la conexión con Steam.
Volviendo al menú de título...</text>
<text id="4161">Velocidad de fotogramas no apta para jugar en línea.
Volviendo al menú de título...</text>
<text id="4190">Se produjo un error de red.
Volviendo al menú de título...</text>
<text id="4191">No se pudo guardar la partida.
Los datos guardados están dañados.

Selecciona Sí para reintentarlo.

Selecciona No para volver
al menú de título sin guardar.</text>
<text id="4192">No se pudo guardar la partida.
Los datos guardados están dañados.

Volviendo al menú de título...</text>
<text id="4193">No se pudo guardar la partida.
Los datos guardados están dañados.</text>
<text id="20023">Registra el gesto en la parte superior del menú principal
para un acceso rápido.</text>
<text id="100000">RB</text>
<text id="100001">LB</text>
<text id="100002">RT</text>
<text id="100003">LT</text>
<text id="100004">%null%</text>
<text id="100005">%null%</text>
<text id="100006">%null%</text>
<text id="100007">%null%</text>
<text id="100008">%null%</text>
<text id="100009">%null%</text>
<text id="100010">Gamertag</text>
<text id="100011">Nombre del personaje</text>
<text id="101000">PRESIONA UN BOTÓN</text>
<text id="102000">TIENDA DE DLC</text>
<text id="110000">Configuración del control</text>
<text id="110001">%null%</text>
<text id="110002">%null%</text>
<text id="110003">%null%</text>
<text id="110004">%null%</text>
<text id="110005">%null%</text>
<text id="110006">%null%</text>
<text id="110007">%null%</text>
<text id="110008">%null%</text>
<text id="110009">%null%</text>
<text id="110010">Vibración del control</text>
<text id="111030">Configuración de botones</text>
<text id="111031">%null%</text>
<text id="111032">%null%</text>
<text id="111033">%null%</text>
<text id="111034">%null%</text>
<text id="111035">Configuración de botones</text>
<text id="120200">%null%</text>
<text id="200100">El texto contiene caracteres no admitidos.
Estos se reemplazarán por asteriscos (*).</text>
<text id="280000">Esta asignación de teclas no se puede eliminar.</text>
<text id="280001">%null%</text>
<text id="280002">Revisa los ajustes. 
Una o más teclas están asignadas a más de una función.</text>
<text id="280003">Una o más teclas están asignadas a más de una función.
¿Salir del menú sin guardar?</text>
<text id="400003">Al finalizar la sesión anterior, no seleccionaste Salir del juego o Volver al escritorio desde el menú de Sistema. Usa una de estas opciones cuando quieras finalizar tu sesión de juego.
Si no usas una de estas opciones para finalizar la sesión, podrías perder tu progreso.</text>
<text id="401102">No se pudieron crear los datos de guardado.
Selecciona ACEPTAR para reintentarlo.</text>
<text id="401103">No se pudieron cargar los datos de guardado.
Selecciona ACEPTAR para reintentarlo.</text>
<text id="401104">%null%</text>
<text id="401105">%null%</text>
<text id="401106">No se pudo guardar la partida.
Los datos están dañados.

Selecciona ACEPTAR para reintentarlo.</text>
<text id="401107">Los datos guardados están dañados.
¿Quieres eliminarlos y crear datos nuevos?</text>
<text id="401108">%null%</text>
<text id="401109">%null%</text>
<text id="401110">Comprobando datos guardados…</text>
<text id="401111">Creando datos guardados…</text>
<text id="401112">Actualizando datos guardados…</text>
<text id="401113">La versión del juego no coincide con la de los datos guardados.
Sal del juego y usa el cliente de Steam
para actualizarlo a la versión más reciente.</text>
<text id="401114">Este perfil corresponde a una versión más actual del juego y
no se puede cargar en la versión en ejecución.
Sal del juego e inicia sesión en Steam para actualizar los datos del juego
a su versión más reciente.</text>
<text id="401115">%null%</text>
<text id="401116">%null%</text>
<text id="401117">%null%</text>
<text id="401118">%null%</text>
<text id="401119">%null%</text>
<text id="401120">Comprobando estado de conexión de red…</text>
<text id="401150">Iniciando sesión en el servidor de juego de ELDEN RING…</text>
<text id="401151">%null%</text>
<text id="401152">%null%</text>
<text id="401153">%null%</text>
<text id="401154">%null%</text>
<text id="401155">%null%</text>
<text id="401156">%null%</text>
<text id="401157">%null%</text>
<text id="401158">%null%</text>
<text id="401159">%null%</text>
<text id="401160">Recuperando datos del servidor de juego de ELDEN RING…</text>
<text id="401161">%null%</text>
<text id="401162">%null%</text>
<text id="401163">%null%</text>
<text id="401164">%null%</text>
<text id="401165">Guardando datos en el servidor de juego de ELDEN RING…</text>
<text id="401166">%null%</text>
<text id="401167">%null%</text>
<text id="401168">%null%</text>
<text id="401169">%null%</text>
<text id="401170">Iniciarás el juego sin conexión.

Para usar las características de red, 
comprueba que la conexión esté bien configurada 
y selecciona INICIAR SESIÓN en el menú de título.</text>
<text id="401171">Volviendo al menú de título...</text>
<text id="401172">La versión de prueba de red de ELDEN RING
solo puede jugarse en línea.
Regresando al menú de título...</text>
<text id="401201">No se puede conectar con la red.
Comprueba la configuración.</text>
<text id="401202">Falló la comprobación de estado de red.</text>
<text id="401310">Se ha instalado el nuevo contenido descargable.
Debes volver al menú del título para ver este contenido en el juego.
Selecciona "ACEPTAR" para volver al menú de título.</text>
<text id="401400">No se puede jugar en línea porque se detectó un problema de velocidad de fotogramas.

Resuelve el problema y reinicia el juego para jugar en línea.</text>
<text id="401401">Se detectó una actividad inapropiada.
No se puede iniciar el modo en línea.</text>
<text id="401402">Se detectó una actividad inapropiada.
Regresando al menú de título.</text>
<text id="401403">Falló la conexión a Epic Online Services: &lt;?errcodeEOS?&gt;
No se ha podido iniciar en modo online.</text>
<text id="401404">Falló la conexión a Steamworks: &lt;?errcodeSteam?&gt;
No se ha podido iniciar en modo online.</text>
<text id="401405">Falló la conexión a Epic Online Services: &lt;?errcodeEOS?&gt;
Volviendo al menú principal.</text>
<text id="401502">La cuenta no tiene acceso a los servicios
del servidor de juego de ELDEN RING.</text>
<text id="401503">No se pudo iniciar sesión en el servidor de juego
de ELDEN RING. Selecciona ACEPTAR para reintentarlo.</text>
<text id="401504">Está disponible una actualización del juego. Para usar
las características de red, instala la actualización y reinicia el juego.</text>
<text id="401505">No se puede iniciar sesión en el servidor de juego
de ELDEN RING porque está desactivado temporalmente
o en mantenimiento.</text>
<text id="401506">%null%</text>
<text id="401507">Valve Anti-Cheat detectó que se hizo trampa con tu cuenta.
Ya no puedes usar los servicios que proporcionan
los servidores de juego de ELDEN RING.</text>
<text id="401601">No se pudo adquirir la información
Selecciona ACEPTAR para reintentarlo.</text>
<text id="401701">No se puede crear más perfiles.
¿Quieres eliminar un perfil existente y crear uno nuevo?

Nota: Puedes crear hasta 10 perfiles.</text>
<text id="401721">No se pudieron cargar los datos guardados.
Están dañados.</text>
<text id="401722">%null%</text>
<text id="401723">%null%</text>
<text id="401724">%null%</text>
<text id="401725">%null%</text>
<text id="401726">%null%</text>
<text id="401727">%null%</text>
<text id="401728">%null%</text>
<text id="401729">%null%</text>
<text id="401730">%null%</text>
<text id="401731">No se pudieron inicializar los datos de personaje para jugar en línea.
Selecciona ACEPTAR para reintentarlo.</text>
<text id="401991">Se produjo un error.
Volviendo al menú de título...</text>
<text id="600000">These Terms of Service (hereinafter referred to as the "TOS") shall apply to any matters between Players, as defined in the TOS, and FromSoftware, Inc. (hereinafter referred to as the "Company") of the use of online services (hereinafter referred to as the "Services") for the game software, "ELDEN RING" (hereinafter referred to as the "Software") developed by the Company. Players shall use the Services in accordance with the TOS. Should any Player fail to consent to the TOS, such Player may not use the Services. Players shall be deemed to have consented to the TOS when using the Services.

</text>
<text id="600001">Article 1. Scope and Modification of TOS
1. The Company may, in addition to the TOS, separately notify Players of terms of use, precautions, guidelines and other terms and conditions (hereinafter referred to as "Individual Terms") where appropriate by posting Individual Terms on the official website operated by the Company (hereinafter referred to as the "Website") or through other means. Individual Terms shall constitute part of the TOS, and if any provision of Individual Terms conflicts with the TOS, the provision of Individual Terms shall apply and supersede the TOS.
2. The Company shall be entitled to modify or revise the TOS and Individual Terms where appropriate from time to time, and in this case, may notify Players of such modification or revision by posting the same on the Website or through other means the Company thinks it reasonable.
3. If any Player fails to consent to the modification or revision of the TOS and Individual Terms, the Company shall be entitled to have the Player cease or suspend his/her use of the Services.
4. Players shall be deemed to have consented to the modified or revised the TOS through their continuous use of the Services after the Players have been notified of such modification or revision through any means set forth in Paragraph 1 of this Article.
5. When Players use the Services, the necessary terms and conditions for the use of STEAM® shall apply.

</text>
<text id="600002">Article 2. Definition of Players
The term "Player" means a customer who consents to the TOS (in the plural, "Players"). Players less than twenty (20) years of age shall be deemed to have obtained the consent of their parents or other persons who have parental authority when consenting to the TOS.

</text>
<text id="600003">Article 3. Principle of Self-responsibility
1. Players shall use the Services at their own responsibility, and if any Player causes any loss or damage to another or the Company when using the Services, the Player shall pay damages therefor at his/her own expense and responsibility.
2. Players shall, when giving and receiving any information or service to and from any third party other than the Company through the Services, be fully liable for any acts and contents incidental thereto. If any Player causes any loss or damage to another or to the Company when giving and receiving any such information or service, the Player shall pay damages therefor at his/her own expense and responsibility.
3. Players shall, if any problem arises through the Services with any third party other than the Company, deal with and resolve the problem at their own expense and responsibility. The Company shall not be obligated or liable in any way whatsoever for arbitration, dealing, compensation, damages or any other matters with respect to such problem.

</text>
<text id="600004">Article 4. Liability for Fees and Charges
1. The Services are free of charge; however, Players shall prepare the necessary hardware, lines and any other items for their use of the Services at their own expense and responsibility.
2. Fees for the Software and contents and services provided accompanying the Services will be determined by the Company at its discretion depending on the details and time of such provision.

</text>
<text id="600005">Article 5. Management of Personal Information
1. For the protection of personal information, Players shall not include information that leads to his/her identification in any information posted or disclosed by him/her through the Services when using the Services.
2. The Company shall not protect information posted on or disclosed in the Services.

</text>
<text id="600006">Article 6. Ownership of Rights
1. Any rights in and to the Software and the Services, including intellectual property rights (any and all rights including, but not limited to patent rights, utility model rights, trademark rights, design rights, knowhow, trade secrets and copyrights) shall belong to the Company or the third parties in question.
2. Players shall not be entitled to alter, adapt, copy, edit, reproduce, distribute, transmit or publish all pieces of information included in the Software and the Services (any and all kinds of information including, but not limited to images, pictures, characters, scenarios, plots, programs, software and ideas) without the prior approval of the Company.
3. When using the Services, Players shall not have any intellectual property right or claim with respect to data stored on any storage device such as a server for the Services (hereinafter referred to as "Recorded Data"), and Players hereby grant the Company or the third party designated by the Company the right to copy, edit and distribute Recorded Data.

</text>
<text id="600007">Article 7. Outsourcing of Operation of the Services
The Company shall be entitled to assign to another all or any part of its rights and obligations related to the operation of the Services or outsource to another the operation of all or any part of the Services.

</text>
<text id="600008">Article 8. Suspension of the Services
The Company shall, in cases falling under the following items, suspend any part or all of the Services without prior notice to Players:
(1) Where any failure or other defect occurs in any of the systems used for the Services (including, but not limited to communication lines, power sources, and any structures where the foregoing is accommodated);
(2) Where maintenance, inspection, repair or modification work is regularly or urgently carried out on any systems used for the Services;
(3) Where services for STEAM® cease or are suspended; or
(4) Otherwise where the Company determines that it is necessary to suspend the Services for operational or technical reasons.

</text>
<text id="600009">Article 9 Discontinuation of Provision of the Services
The Company shall, at any time upon giving prior notice of termination to Players, be entitled to discontinue the provision of all or any part of the Services. In this case, the Company shall notify Players of that fact by posting the same on the Website, by e-mail or through other means the Company thinks reasonable. The notice of termination shall be deemed to have reached all Players upon expiration of thirty (30) days after the Company has started posting such notice on the Website.

</text>
<text id="600010">Article 10 Prohibited Matters
1. No Player shall be entitled to assign to, transfer to, sell to or buy from another, change the name to another's name of, or provide another as pledge or other security with, any of his/her rights held as a Player, and items, characters and saved data within the game related to the Software which are obtained in the Services (including so-called "real money trading").
2. No Player shall perform any of the following other acts on the Services:
(1) Playing a game in a manner offensive to other Players;
(2) Playing a game using falsified data regardless of the circumstances;
(3) Playing a game in a manner not intended by the Company using any function or failure of the Software or the Services; or
(4) Performing any other act determined to be inappropriate by the Company or a third party providing any of the systems used for the Services.
3. With respect to Players who have performed acts prohibited under this Article, the Company or the third party providing any of the systems used for the Services shall be entitled at its discretion to give such Players warnings, delete the Recorded Data of such Players, or have such Players suspend or cease their use of the Services.

</text>
<text id="600011">Article 11 Third-Party Software: Easy Anti-Cheat
The company shall employ the use of the “Easy Anti-Cheat” anti-cheat service (hereinafter referred to as "EAC”) for the sake of preventing acts detailed to in Article 10, Section 2., Subsections (2), (3) and (4). EAC is operated by a third-party service provider. EAC has a client software that is integrated into the Software. When starting the Software, the EAC client software will automatically load and install its latest version to the Hardware. EAC will monitor the Hardware, analyze the Software binaries and scan Hardware memory for the purpose of detecting and preventing cheating in the Software (hereinafter referred to as the “Purpose”). For the Purpose, EAC stores information regarding cheating methods used in the Software (hereinafter referred to as “Cheat Data”). By agreeing to this Agreement, or otherwise using the Software or the Services, the Player gives their consent that EAC may gather, store, share, and publish Cheat Data for the Purpose. The Cheat Data will be used solely for the Purpose. This includes but is not limited to identifying and banning Players who are cheating in the Software or the Services, analyzing cheating behavior and cheating codes, as well as sharing data about cheats with affiliates of EAC.
You can find more information about the privacy practices of EAC by viewing the privacy statement of EAC service provider EPIC GAMES (https://www.epicgames.com/site/ja/privacypolicy). If the Player denies EAC the ability to process personal data in accordance with their privacy statement or requests EAC to remove or delete personal data, the Company has the right to block the Player’s access to the Software or the Services and prevent use of the Software or the Services.

</text>
<text id="600012">Article 12 Damages
1. Excluding cases of bad faith or gross negligence, the Company shall not be liable in any way to Players for any loss or damage caused to Players and third parties due to the Players' use of the Services, nor shall the Company be obligated to pay damages therefor.
2. With respect to the deletion of the Recorded Data of Players, the cessation or cancellation of Players' registration, or the cessation, suspension or discontinuation of Players' use of the Services by the Company, the Company shall not be obligated to pay any damages, unless the Company acts in bad faith or gross negligence.
3. Even if the Company is liable for damages for any reason, the Company shall not be liable to pay damages of an amount exceeding those for the loss or damage directly caused to Players, nor shall the Company be liable to pay damages for any incidental, indirect, special or future damage, or lost profits.
4. If any Player causes any loss or damage to other Players or third parties due to his/her use of the Services, the Player shall resolve such issue at his/her own expense and responsibility, and not cause any loss or damage to the Company.
5. If any Player causes any loss or damage to the Company due to his/her act in violation of the TOS or his/her improper or illegal actions, the Company shall be entitled to make a claim for damages against the Player.

</text>
<text id="600013">Article 13 Disclaimers
1. Each Player shall, if another makes any inquiry or complaint to him/her in connection with his/her use of the Services, or he/she has any request, question or complaint about another's act, deal with and resolve such issue at his/her own expense and responsibility, and the Company shall not be liable or obligated in any way therefor.
2. Players shall note that they will avoid using the Services at their discretion in an excessive manner that may disturb their sound lifestyle. The Company shall not be liable in any way for any social, mental or physical damage caused to any Player due to the Player's deviant behavior therefrom.
3. For conflicts of interests or problems between Players arising in connection with the Players' use of the Services, or for measures taken thereunder by the Company or third parties, the Company shall not be liable in any way whatsoever.
4. Since there is a possibility for the Services to be unavailable depending on the individual environment of each Player due to the nature of the Services, the Company shall not warrant that the Services will be available in any environment.
5. The Company shall not warrant in any way that the Services are free of errors or viruses, or otherwise games will progress in a safe manner.

</text>
<text id="600014">Article 14 Governing Law and Dispute Resolution
The TOS shall, including the execution, validity, interpretation and performance hereof, be governed by the laws and regulations of Japan by all means. If any problem, dispute, difficulty or other issue arises in connection with the Services between any Player and the Company, the Player and the Company shall resolve the issue through consultation in good faith, and in the event of a failure in resolving it through consultation, it shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Tokyo District Court in the first instance as agreed upon between the parties.

</text>
<text id="600015">


Supplementary Provisions
The TOS shall come into effect upon sale of the Software.
The TOS may be modified from time to time.
The latest information shall be posted on the Website and made referenceable by Players from time to time.</text>
<text id="600016">%null%</text>
<text id="601000">Terms and Conditions</text>
<text id="602000">Terms and Conditions</text>
<text id="603000">Terms and Conditions</text>
<text id="606000">&lt;?kgUD?&gt;: Desplazar &lt;?kgLR?&gt;: Seleccionar &lt;?kgOk?&gt;: Confirmar</text>
<text id="606001">Aceptar</text>
<text id="606002">Rechazar</text>
<text id="606003">&lt;?kgUD?&gt;: Seleccionar &lt;?kgOk?&gt;: Confirmar &lt;?kgCancel?&gt;: Cerrar</text>
<text id="606004">Cambiar idioma</text>
<text id="606005">日本語</text>
<text id="606006">Inglés</text>
<text id="606007">Français</text>
<text id="606008">Español</text>
<text id="606009">Italiano</text>
<text id="606010">Deutsch</text>
<text id="606011">한국어</text>
<text id="606012">繁體中文</text>
<text id="606013">简体中文</text>
<text id="606014">Polski</text>
<text id="606015">Русский</text>
<text id="606016">Português (Brasil)</text>
<text id="606017">Español (América Latina)</text>
<text id="606018">ภาษา​ไทย</text>
</entries>
</fmg>