<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<fmg>
<compression>None</compression>
<version>DarkSouls3</version>
<bigendian>False</bigendian>
<entries>
<text id="1">-</text>
<text id="2">%null%</text>
<text id="3">%null%</text>
<text id="4">%null%</text>
<text id="5">%null%</text>
<text id="6">%null%</text>
<text id="7">%null%</text>
<text id="8">%null%</text>
<text id="9">%null%</text>
<text id="10">No skill.

This armament has no skill.
If the armament in the other hand has a skill, that skill will be used instead.</text>
<text id="100">Skill: Lion's Claw

Skill of the Redmanes, who fought alongside General Radahn.
Somersault forwards, striking foes with armament.</text>
<text id="101">Skill: Impaling Thrust

Skill that lets piercing armaments overcome enemy shields. Build power, then lunge forward for a strong thrust that pierces an enemy's guard.</text>
<text id="102">Skill: Piercing Fang

Skill used by Yura, the Bloody Finger Hunter.
Starting with the blade held horizontally, make a powerful thrust that cannot be blocked.</text>
<text id="103">Skill: Spinning Slash

Skill favored by dexterous warriors.
Slash foes as your body spins. Additional input allows for a follow-up attack.</text>
<text id="104">Skill: Spinning Reaper

Skill developed to face crowds of enemies.
Slice at foes while performing a great
rotation with the body. The momentum
generated can empower a final, heavy strike.</text>
<text id="105">Skill: Charge Forth

Quickly charge forward with the armament at the hip, carrying the momentum into a thrust.
Hold to cover a greater distance.</text>
<text id="106">Skill: Stamp (Upward Cut)

Brace armament and step into a low stance that prevents recoil from most enemy attacks.
Follow up with a strong attack for an upward strike.</text>
<text id="107">Skill: Stamp (Sweep)

Brace armament and step into a low stance that prevents recoil from most enemy attacks.
Follow up with a strong attack for a sweeping strike.</text>
<text id="108">Skill: Blood Tax

Blood Oath skill granted by the Lord of Blood.
Twist to build power, then unleash a flurry of thrusts that rob the target of both their blood and their HP.</text>
<text id="109">Skill: Repeating Thrust

Twist to build power, then unleash a flurry of thrusts.</text>
<text id="110">Skill: Wild Strikes

Swing armament with wild abandon.
Hold to continue swinging. Can be followed up with a normal or strong attack.</text>
<text id="111">Skill: Spinning Strikes

Polearm skill that performs continuous spinning attacks. Hold to continue the attack. Can be followed up with a normal or strong attack. Nullifies projectiles such as arrows while spinning.</text>
<text id="112">Skill: Double Slash

Skill of superior swordsmen.
Perform a crossing slash attack from a low stance.
Repeated inputs allow for up to two follow-up attacks.</text>
<text id="113">Skill: Prelate's Charge

Slam armament into the ground to create a surge of flames, then charge in.
Hold to continue the charge.</text>
<text id="114">Skill: Unsheathe

Skill of swordsmen from the Land of Reeds.
Sheathe blade, holding it at the hip in a composed stance.
Follow up with a normal or strong attack to perform a swift slash attack.</text>
<text id="115">Skill: Square Off

This skill starts with the sword held level.
Follow up with a normal attack to slash upwards through enemy's guard, or a strong attack to perform a running thrust.</text>
<text id="116">Skill: Giant Hunt

Skill developed for confronting gigantic foes.
Step forward from a low stance, carrying the momentum into a sudden upward thrust.</text>
<text id="117">Skill: Torch Attack

Thrust torch forward to set foes ablaze.
This skill is especially effective against foes who are weak to fire.</text>
<text id="118">Skill: Loretta's Slash

Skill of Loretta the Royal Knight.
Leap forward, imbuing the blade with glintstone, then descend, accelerating into a sweeping slash.</text>
<text id="119">Skill: Poison Moth Flight

Slash with a poison-infused blade.
If the follow-up strike lands on a poisoned foe, it will deal significant damage.</text>
<text id="120">Skill: Spinning Weapon

Defensive skill employed by Carian princesses.
Lifts armament into mid-air, then makes it spin violently. Those it touches will suffer successive attacks.</text>
<text id="121">%null%</text>
<text id="122">Skill: Storm Assault

One of the skills that channel the tempests of Stormveil.
Leap forward through surrounding storm winds and thrust armament downward. The attack will produce more storm winds at the point of impact.</text>
<text id="123">Skill: Stormcaller

One of the skills that channel the tempests of Stormveil. Spin armament to create surrounding storm winds. Repeated inputs allow for up to two follow-up attacks.</text>
<text id="124">Skill: Sword Dance

Quickly close in to perform a series of spinning upward slashes.
Follow up with an additional input to finish with a downward slash.</text>
<text id="125">Skill: Spinning Chain

Spins the striking part of a flail at high speed to attack.
Follow up with a normal or strong attack to link the momentum of this skill into a successive attack.</text>
<text id="200">Skill: Glintblade Phalanx

Skill used by the enchanted knights who served the Carian royal family. Form an arch of magic glintblades overhead, which will attack foes automatically. Follow up with a strong attack to chain this skill into a lunging thrust.</text>
<text id="201">Skill: Sacred Blade

Grants armament's attacks holy essence and fires off a golden blade projectile.
The armament retains its holy essence for a while.</text>
<text id="202">Skill: Ice Spear

Skill of the warriors who served Lunar Princess Ranni.
Spin armament to release cold magic, then channel it into a piercing spear of ice.</text>
<text id="203">Skill: Glintstone Pebble

Skill that employs the glintstone sorcery of the same name.
Follow up with a strong attack to chain this skill into a lunging thrust, performed while the armament is still imbued with glintstone.</text>
<text id="204">Skill: Bloody Slash

Blood Oath skill granted by the Lord of Blood.
From a low stance, coat the blade in your own blood to unleash a rending blood slash in a wide arc.</text>
<text id="205">Skill: Lifesteal Fist

Skill that demonstrates mastery of the art of controlling vital energies.
A slow, controlled punch with an energy-infused fist that renders foes unconscious and steals their HP. Only effective against foes of human build.</text>
<text id="206">%null%</text>
<text id="207">Skill: Eruption

Skill of the knights who serve at Volcano Manor.
Slam armament into the ground, spawning roiling lava which spouts up upon release.</text>
<text id="208">Skill: Prayerful Strike

Raise armament aloft in prayer, then slam it into the ground.
This inspired blow restores HP to the self and nearby allies if it successfully hits.</text>
<text id="209">Skill: Gravitas

Skill originating from the Alabaster Lords, who had skin of stone.
Thrust the armament into the ground to create a gravity well.
In addition to dealing damage, this attack pulls enemies in.</text>
<text id="210">Skill: Storm Blade

Lost skill of Stormveil.
Surround armament with shearing storm winds that can be fired forward.
Can be fired in rapid succession.</text>
<text id="211">%null%</text>
<text id="212">Skill: Earthshaker

Thrust armament into the ground, then gather strength to unleash an earth-shaking shockwave.
Follow up with a strong attack to swing the armament in a sweeping strike.</text>
<text id="213">Skill: Golden Land

Thrust armament into the ground, then gather strength to unleash a blast of sacred energy that coalesces into golden darts. Follow up with a strong attack to swing the armament in a sweeping strike.</text>
<text id="214">Skill: Flaming Strike

Skill that emits flame in a wide frontward arc.
Follow up with a strong attack to perform a lunging, sweeping strike.
This will also coat the armament in fire.</text>
<text id="215">%null%</text>
<text id="216">Skill: Thunderbolt

Skill used by the capital's ancient dragon cult.
Raise armament aloft to call down a bolt of lightning.
Can be fired in rapid succession.</text>
<text id="217">Skill: Lightning Slash

Call down a bolt of lightning into armament, then swing it down to create an explosive shock.
The armament retains the lightning enchantment for a while.</text>
<text id="218">Skill: Carian Grandeur

Carian royal prestige embodied in a skill.
Transform blade into a magical greatsword and swing it down.
Can be charged to increase its power by up to two levels.</text>
<text id="219">Skill: Carian Greatsword

Carian royal prestige embodied in a skill.
Transform blade into a magical greatsword and swing it down.
Can be charged to increase its power.</text>
<text id="220">Skill: Vacuum Slice

Lost skill of ancient heroes.
Hold the armament aloft to surround it with a shearing vacuum, then launch it forwards as a blade-like projectile.</text>
<text id="221">Skill: Black Flame Tornado

Spin armament overhead and then plunge it into the ground to summon a raging vortex of black flames.
Hold to create an initial flame tornado while spinning the armament.</text>
<text id="222">Skill: Sacred Ring of Light

Skill used by the commanders of the Cleanrot Knights. Gather a sacred ring of light in the armament, then fire it forwards.
Can be fired in rapid succession.</text>
<text id="223">Skill: Firebreather

Blow into torch flame, spreading flames in a wide frontward arc. The flames on the ground will continue to burn for a short time.</text>
<text id="224">Skill: Blood Blade

Wound self to coat the armament with blood, then unleash an airborne blood blade that causes hemorrhaging.
Can be fired in rapid succession.</text>
<text id="225">Skill: Phantom Slash

Skill inspired by the fond remembrances of the Night's Cavalry. Creates an apparition of the knights' former instructor who guides a joint lunging upward swing. Additional input allows for a follow-up attack.</text>
<text id="226">Skill: Spectral Lance

Skill of the headless Mausoleum Knights.
Hurl a phantasmic spear at foes.</text>
<text id="227">Skill: Chilling Mist

Coat armament in frost, and then slash, spreading frigid mist forwards.
The armament retains its frost for a while.</text>
<text id="228">Skill: Poisonous Mist

Bathe armament in poison, and then slash, spreading toxic mist forwards.
The armament retains its poison for a while.</text>
<text id="300">Skill: Shield Bash

Brace behind shield before using bodyweight to ram foes while maintaining guarding stance.
Weaker enemies will be shoved backwards, and can even be staggered.</text>
<text id="301">Skill: Barricade Shield

Skill made famous by Sir Neidhardt.
Focus your energy into the shield, temporarily hardening it to deflect greater blows.</text>
<text id="302">Skill: Parry

Use this skill in time with a foe's melee attack to deflect it and break that foe's stance.
This provides an opening to perform a critical hit.</text>
<text id="303">Skill: Buckler Parry

Use this skill in time with a foe's melee attack to deflect it and break that foe's stance.
This is faster than a regular parry.</text>
<text id="304">Skill: Parry

Use this skill in time with a foe's melee attack to deflect it and break that foe's stance.
This provides an opening to perform a critical hit.</text>
<text id="305">Skill: Carian Retaliation

Swing the shield to dispel incoming sorceries and incantations, transforming the magic into retaliatory glintblades.
Can also be used in the same way as a regular parry.</text>
<text id="306">Skill: Storm Wall

Swing the shield to create a wall of storm winds in front of you, deflecting arrows and other such physical projectiles.
Can also be used in the same way as a regular parry.</text>
<text id="307">Skill: Golden Parry

Perform an Erdtree incantation and swing the shield to deflect enemy attacks and break their stance.
Effective even at a slight distance.</text>
<text id="308">Skill: Shield Crash

Two-hand the shield and charge forwards while maintaining guard. Weaker enemies will be shoved backwards and can even be staggered.
Hold to extend the duration of the charge forwards.</text>
<text id="309">Skill: Thops's Barrier

Erect a magical forcefield while swinging the shield to deflect sorceries and incantations.
Can also be used in the same way as a regular parry.</text>
<text id="400">Skill: Through and Through

Powerful archery skill using a greatbow held in an oblique stance.
Ready the greatbow, then twist the bowstring to fire a mighty greatarrow that can penetrate through enemies.</text>
<text id="401">Skill: Barrage

Archery skill using a bow held horizontally.
Ready the bow, then fire off a rapid succession of shots faster than the eye can see.</text>
<text id="402">Skill: Mighty Shot

Archery skill performed from an oblique stance.
Ready the bow, then pull the bowstring to its limit to enhance the power of the shot, penetrating the enemy's guard.</text>
<text id="403">%null%</text>
<text id="404">Skill: Enchanted Shot

Archery skill that enlivens the arrow with spiritual essence.
The resulting shot will fly faster than regular shots and change its trajectory to follow the target.</text>
<text id="405">Skill: Sky Shot

Archery skill performed from a low stance.
Ready the bow, then fire an arrow high up into the air, arcing so as to strike the enemy from above when it comes down.</text>
<text id="406">Skill: Rain of Arrows

Archery skill performed from a low stance.
Ready the bow, then fire a burst of arrows into the sky to shower the enemy with projectiles.</text>
<text id="407">Skill: Invisible Arrow

Nearly invisible magic arrow that leaves
no trail and disappears on impact.</text>
<text id="501">Skill: Hoarfrost Stomp

Stomp hard to spread a trail of freezing mist on the ground.
The mist applies the frost status effect.</text>
<text id="502">Skill: Storm Stomp

One of the skills that channel the tempests of Stormveil.
Stomp hard on the ground to kick up a momentary storm.</text>
<text id="503">Skill: Kick

Push an enemy back with a high kick.
Effective against enemies who are guarding, and can break a foe's stance.
Sometimes a simple tool is the most effective.</text>
<text id="504">Skill: Lightning Ram

Skill inspired by tumbling rams.
Let out a bleat, then tumble forwards, clad in lightning.
Tumbles can be repeated in rapid succession.</text>
<text id="505">Skill: Flame of the Redmanes

Skill of the Redmanes, who fought alongside General Radahn.
Produce a powerful burst of flames in a wide frontward arc.</text>
<text id="506">Skill: Ground Slam

Jump up high into the air and crash down on the ground ahead.
The resulting pratfall sends a powerful shockwave in all directions.</text>
<text id="507">Skill: Golden Slam

Skill of the avatars who protect Minor Erdtrees.
Jump up high into the air and crash down on the ground ahead.
The resulting pratfall sends golden shockwaves in all directions.</text>
<text id="508">Skill: Waves of Darkness

Plunge armament into the ground to release three waves of darkness.
Follow up with a strong attack to swing the armament in a sweeping strike.</text>
<text id="509">Skill: Hoarah Loux's Earthshaker

Slam both hands onto the ground to violently shake the earth and unleash a shockwave.
Follow up with an additional input to slam the ground again.</text>
<text id="600">Skill: Determination

A knightly skill.
Hold the flat of the armament to your face and pledge your resolve, powering up your next attack.</text>
<text id="601">Skill: Royal Knight's Resolve

Skill of the knights who once served the Elden Lord.
Hold the flat of the armament to your face and pledge your resolve, greatly powering up your next attack.</text>
<text id="602">Skill: Assassin's Gambit

Skill that masks the user's presence at the cost of a self-inflicted wound.
Grants near-invisibility and silences footsteps.</text>
<text id="603">Skill: Golden Vow

Skill passed down from antiquity among the knights of the capital. Raise armament aloft and pledge to honor the Erdtree in battle, granting self and nearby allies increased attack power and defense.</text>
<text id="604">Skill: Sacred Order

Skill of the Golden Order fundamentalist knights.
Perform a salute and grant the armament holy essence.
Highly effective against Those Who Live in Death.</text>
<text id="605">Skill: Shared Order

Skill of the Golden Order fundamentalist knights.
Grant the armament and those of nearby allies holy essence.
Highly effective against Those Who Live in Death.</text>
<text id="606">Skill: Seppuku

A forbidden technique used by swordsmen from the Land of Reeds. Plunge the blade into your stomach to stain it with blood. Increases attack power and improves ability to inflict blood loss.</text>
<text id="607">Skill: Cragblade

Skill that manipulates gravity.
Bury the armament in the ground, pulling rocks from the earth to reinforce it. Increases attack power and makes it easier to break enemy stance.</text>
<text id="650">Skill: Barbaric Roar

Let loose a bestial roar to rally the spirit and increase attack power.
While active, strong attacks change to savage combo attacks.</text>
<text id="651">Skill: War Cry

Give a war cry to rally the spirit and increase attack power.
While active, strong attacks change to charging attacks.</text>
<text id="652">Skill: Beast's Roar

Unleash a beastly roar, rending the air as a forward-travelling projectile.</text>
<text id="653">Skill: Troll's Roar

Look into the distance and let out an intense roar, generating a powerful shockwave that blows back surrounding foes.
Follow up with a strong attack to slam the armament down.</text>
<text id="654">Skill: Braggart's Roar

Declare your presence with a boastful roar.
Raises attack power, defense, and stamina recovery speed.</text>
<text id="700">Skill: Endure

Assume an anchored stance to brace for incoming attacks, briefly boosting poise.
Damage taken while using this skill is reduced.</text>
<text id="701">Skill: Vow of the Indomitable

Skill of the ancient warriors of the Erdtree.
Hold shield aloft to imbue yourself with golden power, granting momentary invincibility.</text>
<text id="702">Skill: Holy Ground

Raise shield to create an Erdtree-consecrated area that continuously restores HP and boosts defense for self and allies inside it.</text>
<text id="800">Skill: Quickstep

Skill prized by the crafty and fleet of foot.
Perform a quickstep maneuver that allows for circling around lock-on targets.</text>
<text id="801">Skill: Bloodhound's Step

Skill that allows the user to become temporarily invisible while dodging at high speed. Moves faster and travels farther than a regular quickstep.
This skill can be used to circle around lock-on targets.</text>
<text id="802">Skill: Raptor of the Mists

Duck into a low stance, momentarily vanishing.
If an enemy attack connects, avian wings will allow for a quick escape into the air.</text>
<text id="850">Skill: White Shadow's Lure

Hold armament in a brief, silent prayer to create a white shadow.
The apparition lures in foes of human build who are not in combat, drawing their aggression. Effective on demi-humans even if they are already in a combat state.</text>
<text id="1000">Unique Skill: Surge of Faith

Set the flames of Birac's faith ablaze in the cranial vessel, then raise it aloft to rain down fireballs in all directions.
Repeated inputs will continue to raise the armament aloft, continuing the attack.</text>
<text id="1001">Unique Skill: Flame Spit

Ready the shield, then launch a fireball from the barrel.
The fireball explodes on impact.</text>
<text id="1002">Unique Skill: Tongues of Fire

Ready the shield, then spray violent jets of fire from the tongues protruding from its maw.
Hold to continue spraying fire. This skill can be used while walking.</text>
<text id="1003">Unique Skill: Oracular Bubble

Blow on the horn to release a magic bubble.
The bubble floats gently through the air towards its target.</text>
<text id="1004">Unique Skill: Bubble Shower

Blow on the horn to release a spume of magic bubbles.
The bubbles float gently before raining down on the target.</text>
<text id="1005">Unique Skill: Great Oracular Bubble

Blow on the horn to release a massive magic bubble.
The bubble floats gently through the air towards its target.</text>
<text id="1006">Unique Skill: Sea of Magma

Swing a molten whip overhead to temporarily cover the surrounding area in a sea of magma.
Hold to continue swinging the lava whip.</text>
<text id="1007">Unique Skill: Viper Bite

Give the shield a quick shake to temporarily bring the bronze viper to life, inciting it to lash out and bite foes.</text>
<text id="1008">Unique Skill: Moonlight Greatsword

Raise the sword aloft, bathing it in the light of the dark moon.
Temporarily increases magic attack power and imbues blade with frost.
Charged attacks release blasts of moonlight.</text>
<text id="1009">Unique Skill: Siluria's Woe

Thrust the treespear in a spiraling motion, surrounding it in a vortex of wind.
Charged attacks have the power to blow away enemies and can fire the tornado forwards.</text>
<text id="1010">Unique Skill: Rallying Standard

Hoist the war banner aloft and give a rallying command.
Raises attack power and defense for self and nearby allies.</text>
<text id="1011">Unique Skill: Bear Witness!

Grant the small dragon a fleeting glimpse of life and thrust it skyward, spewing flames over a wide frontward area.</text>
<text id="1012">Unique Skill: Eochaid's Dancing Blade

Infuse the sword with energy, then fling it forwards in a corkscrew attack. The sword continuously deals damage while violently spinning.
Charge the attack to increase reach and duration of the spin.</text>
<text id="1013">Unique Skill: Soul Stifler

Raise the greathorn's wings to summon a soul-sapping miasma.
Enemies in the affected area will temporarily suffer from reduced defense.</text>
<text id="1014">Unique Skill: Taker's Flames

Raise the sacred sword aloft to set it ablaze with blasphemous flames, then bring it down to fire off a forward blast.
The flames steal HP from those they touch.</text>
<text id="1015">Unique Skill: Shriek of Milos

Lets out a horrific cursed scream that reduces all damage negation and status resistances for nearby foes.
While active, strong attacks will change to a combo attack.</text>
<text id="1016">Unique Skill: Reduvia Blood Blade

Slash with the wicked dagger, transforming its never-drying bloodstains into airborne blood blades that cause hemorrhaging.
Can be fired in rapid succession.</text>
<text id="1017">Unique Skill: Glintstone Dart

Skill that builds from the Glintstone Pebble sorcery.
Charge the skill to upgrade it to Glintstone Dart.
Follow up with a strong attack to chain this skill into a lunging thrust.</text>
<text id="1018">Unique Skill: Flowing Form

Temporarily transforms armament into its liquid form.
Swing the armament like a whip to perform a sweeping slice over a wide area.</text>
<text id="1019">Unique Skill: Night-and-Flame Stance

Hold the sword level and prepare to cast a sorcery.
Follow up with a normal attack to cast the Night Comet sorcery, or a strong attack to sweep forward with a burst of flames.</text>
<text id="1020">Unique Skill: Wave of Gold

Imbue the sword with bygone golden glory, then fire it at foes.
A wide, golden wave fans out forwards, sweeping through all enemies caught in its path.</text>
<text id="1021">Unique Skill: Ruinous Ghostflame

Swing the sword to bathe its blade in ghostflame.
The ghostflame adds magic damage to attacks, and also has a bitterly cold bite.</text>
<text id="1022">Unique Skill: Establish Order

Raise the armament in a salute, releasing a golden explosion.
Repeated inputs send out waves of golden light.</text>
<text id="1023">Unique Skill: Mists of Slumber

Releases a faint purple mist that spreads across a wide frontwards area.
This mist inflicts the sleep ailment upon foes.</text>
<text id="1024">Unique Skill: Spearcall Ritual

Thrust the spear high, bearing prayers into the sky to summon a downpour of spectral spears.</text>
<text id="1025">Unique Skill: Wolf's Assault

Infuse the greatsword with frost, then perform a forward somersault to plunge it into the ground. Then, pull it out to release a cold blast.</text>
<text id="1026">Unique Skill: Thundercloud Form

Temporarily transform into a red thundercloud and fly through the air, then plunge down with a lightning-infused blade.
Hold to increase the reach of the thundercloud form.</text>
<text id="1027">Unique Skill: Cursed-Blood Slice

Brace, then charge forward to deliver a downward diagonal slice.
The bloody trail of the blade is followed by a burst of flame.
Additional input allows for a follow-up attack.</text>
<text id="1028">Unique Skill: Waterfowl Dance

Perform a series of one-footed leaps in the manner of a waterfowl to unleash a swift yet graceful slashing combo.
Repeated inputs allow for up to two follow-up attacks.</text>
<text id="1029">Unique Skill: Gold Breaker

Leap up high and, while suspended in midair, imbue the rune shard with light before smashing it down hard onto the ground.
The heroic Radagon's signature attack.</text>
<text id="1030">Unique Skill: I Command Thee, Kneel!

Repeatedly smash the Axe of Godrick into the ground, unleashing two earth-shaking shockwaves.
Follow up with an additional input to produce a third shockwave.</text>
<text id="1031">Unique Skill: Regal Roar

Let loose a mighty war cry, raising attack power, while sending out a shockwave that cannot be guarded against by stomping the ground. While active, strong attack becomes a lunging slash.</text>
<text id="1032">Unique Skill: Starcaller Cry

Bring the two swords together and roar into the skies, pulling in enemies with a gravitational wave.
Follow up with an additional input to slam down with gravity-infused swords.</text>
<text id="1033">Unique Skill: Wave of Destruction

Raise the sword up high, then strike it against the ground to fire off a wave of gravitational force.</text>
<text id="1034">Unique Skill: Bloodboon Ritual

Raise the sacred spear and pierce the body of the Formless Mother. Stab up to three times, creating explosions of blood with each thrust.
This skill will coat the armament with bloodflame for a while.</text>
<text id="1035">Unique Skill: Flowing Form

Temporarily transforms armament into its liquid form. Swing the armament like a whip to strike surroundings before slamming its teardrop-shaped head down.</text>
<text id="1036">Unique Skill: Blade of Death

Unleash the power of the Rune of Death to fire off a blade-like projectile.
In addition to dealing immediate damage, the blade reduces the enemy's maximum HP and continues to wear down HP for a while.</text>
<text id="1037">Unique Skill: Blade of Gold

Leap into the air, charging the armament with golden flames that are then shot at the enemy as a single, blade-like projectile.
Inflicts holy damage.</text>
<text id="1038">Unique Skill: Destined Death

Set free the remnants of Destined Death, plunging the greatsword into the ground to summon a myriad of blades. In addition to dealing immediate damage, this attack reduces the enemy's maximum HP and continues to wear down HP for a short time.</text>
<text id="1039">Unique Skill: Spinning Wheel

Strike the wheel against the ground to set it spinning at top speed. Hold to keep the wheel spinning. Can be used while walking to push the armament into enemies.</text>
<text id="1040">Unique Skill: Alabaster Lord's Pull

Thrust the armament into the ground to create a gravity well. In addition to dealing damage, this attack pulls enemies in.
Has a greater area of effect than Gravitas.</text>
<text id="1041">Unique Skill: Onyx Lord's Repulsion

Thrust the armament into the ground to create a gravity well. In addition to dealing damage, this attack sends enemies flying away.</text>
<text id="1042">Unique Skill: Oath of Vengeance

Swear an oath upon the greatsword to avenge the clan, temporarily raising all attributes for a certain duration. While the oath's effects are active, poise will also be increased.</text>
<text id="1043">Unique Skill: Ice Lightning Sword

Call down a bolt of ice lightning into the blade and bring it down upon a foe.
The ice lightning effect will persist for a while.</text>
<text id="1044">Unique Skill: Regal Beastclaw

Slam the hammer into the ground, rending the land asunder with the armament's five bestial claws.</text>
<text id="1045">Unique Skill: Flame Dance

Imbue the red braid with the Giants' Flame and lash out in a wide range with a series of agile swings.</text>
<text id="1046">Unique Skill: Claw Flick

Cause the finger to swell, then flex to build up strength before giving enemies an almighty flick.</text>
<text id="1047">Unique Skill: Nebula

Imbue the Naturalborn's stars with magic to perform a sweeping strike.
This attack leaves a dark cloud of stars in its wake that lingers briefly before exploding.</text>
<text id="1048">Unique Skill: Ghostflame Ignition

Thrust out the barbed rod and set its tip alight with ghostflame.
Follow up with a normal attack to set the ground ablaze with ghostflame, or a strong attack to trigger a massive explosion.</text>
<text id="1049">Unique Skill: Ancient Lightning Spear

Imbue the armament with the ancient dragons' red lightning, then throw it as a spear.
Can be charged to increase its power.</text>
<text id="1050">Unique Skill: Frenzyflame Thrust

Imbue the spear with the flame of frenzy and leap forwards, plunging it into the ground and setting off a maddening explosion.
The skill inflicts both the enemy and the user with madness.</text>
<text id="1051">Unique Skill: Miquella's Ring of Light

Summon Miquella's shining halo and fire it forwards.
Can be fired in rapid succession.</text>
<text id="1052">Unique Skill: Golden Tempering

Cross the two swords to grant their attacks holy essence.
While in effect, strong attack performs a dual-wielding combo attack.</text>
<text id="1053">Unique Skill: Last Rites

Raise the epitaph to grant the effect of Sacred Order to yourself and allies in the vicinity.
Particularly effective at laying to rest Those Who Live in Death.</text>
<text id="1054">Unique Skill: Unblockable Blade

Imbue the cipher blade with light, extending its length, then strike with a sudden sweeping attack.
This attack cannot be blocked.</text>
<text id="1055">Unique Skill: Eochaid's Dancing Blade

Infuse the sword with energy, then fling it forwards in a corkscrew attack. The sword continuously deals damage while violently spinning.
Charge the attack to increase reach and duration of the spin.</text>
<text id="1167">Unique Skill: Corpse Wax Cutter

Lost skill of ancient heroes.
Lift the sword up high to release the power of corpse wax and launch it forwards as a blade-like projectile.
</text>
<text id="1168">Unique Skill: Zamor Ice Storm

Plunge the curved sword into the ground, building power before unleashing a freezing storm that batters the surroundings.</text>
<text id="1169">Unique Skill: Radahn's Rain

Archery skill performed from a low stance.
Ready the bow and fire a sudden flurry of arrows up into the sky. The arrows will pour on foes like rain.</text>
<text id="1170">Unique Skill: The Queen's Black Flame

Set the blade ablaze with the god-slaying black flame before delivering a sweeping slash. Additional input allows for a follow-up attack. The black flames will continue to wear down HP for a while.</text>
<text id="1171">Unique Skill: Dynast's Finesse

Nimbly avoid an attack, securing some distance from foes. Follow up with strong attack to perform a sudden lunge, and press strong attack again to perform a sweeping slice.</text>
<text id="1172">Unique Skill: Magma Shower

Slash at foes in a twirling motion while scattering magma all around.
Additional input allows for a follow-up attack.</text>
<text id="1173">Unique Skill: Nebula

Imbue the Naturalborn's wings with magic to send forth a dark cloud of stars that lingers briefly before exploding.</text>
<text id="1174">Unique Skill: Death Flare

Set the lusterless sun ablaze with the Prince of Death's flames, inflicting the death ailment upon foes.
Follow up with an additional input to bring down the armament, triggering an explosion.</text>
<text id="1175">Unique Skill: Bloodhound's Finesse

Slash upwards with the Bloodhound's Fang, using the momentum of the strike to perform a backwards somersault and gain some distance from foes. Follow up with a strong attack to perform the Bloodhound's Step attack.</text>
<text id="1176">Unique Skill: Magma Guillotine

Grab the scalesword with both hands, as a wyrm would hold it in its mouth, and leap forwards, smashing it into the ground and triggering a blast of magma. Follow up with an additional input to perform a chopping attack.</text>
<text id="1177">Unique Skill: Corpse Piler

Forms a blade of cursed blood for repeated, interweaving successive attacks. Follow up with an additional input for further successive attacks. </text>
<text id="1178">Unique Skill: Transient Moonlight

Sheathe blade, holding it at the hip in a composed stance.
Follow up with either a normal or a strong attack to draw the blade at great speed for an instant slash attack. Both attacks fire off a wave of light.</text>
<text id="1179">Unique Skill: Bloodblade Dance

Leap at foe to perform a flurry of tornado-like attacks.
Follow up with an additional input to perform an attack that ends in an evasive maneuver.</text>
<text id="1180">Skill: Death Monarch

Launch summoned death monarchs at enemies,
siphoning HP from those hit and returning
it to the caster.</text>
<text id="1181">Skill: Miquella's Hidden Blade

Conjures a blade blessed with Miquella's protection, and performs an attack that is highly damaging against those who live in death.</text>
<text id="1182">Unique Skill: Knowledge Above All

Raise the scepter to manifest the realm of the All-Knowing. Enemy magic and holy damage negation will be reduced for all within the area, including the caster.</text>
<text id="1183">Unique Skill: Devourer of Worlds

Charge the scepter with magic and strike it against the ground to steal the HP of all nearby enemies.</text>
<text id="1184">Unique Skill: Familial Rancor

Gently rattle the copper heads to summon vengeful spirits that chase down foes.
The anguish of a spouse and children invites accursed wrath.</text>
<text id="1185">Unique Skill: Rosus's Summons

Raise the axe aloft to summon those lost in death.
Three skeletons will appear at a distance and attack in tandem before vanishing.</text>
<text id="1186">Unique Skill: Thunderstorm

Imbue the armament's wing-blade with lightning and swing it around to create a tempestuous lightning storm. Follow up with an additional input to perform up to two spinning attacks.
The lightning will stay on the blade for a while.</text>
<text id="1187">Unique Skill: Sacred Phalanx

Release the power of a hidden incantation to erect a palisade of golden spears frontwards.</text>
<text id="1188">Unique Skill: Great-Serpent Hunt

Perform a powerful forward lunge and follow up with an upward thrust via additional input. When fighting a great serpent, a long blade of light will appear, revealing the armament's true power.</text>
<text id="1189">Unique Skill: Angel's Wings

Jump and imbue the wing-blade of the armament with light, then deliver a slashing attack on the enemy.
The white wings impede recovery actions using a flask of tears.</text>
<text id="1190">Unique Skill: Storm Kick

Thrust the prosthetic leg blade into the ground, creating a storm.
Follow up with a strong attack to perform a lightning-infused jumping attack.</text>
<text id="1191">Unique Skill: Unblockable Blade

Imbue the cipher blade with light, then lunge forward with a sudden piercing attack.
This attack cannot be blocked.</text>
<text id="1192">Unique Skill: Sorcery of the Crozier

Channel magic into the glintstone to activate an ancient sorcery, producing floating magic projectiles that chase enemies automatically.</text>
<text id="1193">Unique Skill: Erdtree Slam

Jump up high into the air and crash down on the ground ahead. The resulting pratfall sends golden shockwaves in all directions.
This is the most powerful of all the Ground Slam skills.</text>
<text id="1194">Unique Skill: Gravity Bolt

Imbue the jaw of fallingstar beast with gravitational lightning, sending a bolt crashing down a short distance away.
Can be fired in rapid succession.</text>
<text id="1195">Unique Skill: Fires of Slumber

Blow into the candlestick's flame, creating a stream of hazy purple fire to cover the ground ahead.
The intoxicating flames inflict the sleep ailment upon foes.</text>
<text id="1196">Unique Skill: Golden Retaliation

Ready the shield to unleash its protective incantation.
This will dispel sorceries and incantations, retaliating with golden power.</text>
<text id="1197">Unique Skill: Contagious Fury

Incite the jellyfish's wrath and allow its fury to flow through you.
Raises attack power for a certain duration.</text>
<text id="1198">Unique Skill: Ordovis's Vortex

Channel the power of the crucible to spin the entire sword in midair, building momentum before slamming the blade down onto the ground.
This skill can be charged to increase its power.</text>
<text id="1199">Unique Skill: Spinning Weapon

Channel magic into the glintstone to suspend the scepter in mid air and cause it to spin violently.
Those it touches will suffer successive magic attacks.</text>
</entries>
</fmg>